<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Our Blog on Koulutus ja Osaaminen</title><link>https://osaaminen.github.io/blog/</link><description>Recent content in Our Blog on Koulutus ja Osaaminen</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>Copyright &amp;copy; 2021 [osaaminen](https://osaaminen.github.io)</copyright><lastBuildDate>Tue, 12 Jan 2021 12:52:36 +0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://osaaminen.github.io/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>An MBA-equivalent education for free</title><link>https://osaaminen.github.io/blog/mba/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Jan 2021 12:52:36 +0600</pubDate><guid>https://osaaminen.github.io/blog/mba/</guid><description>Back when massive open online courses were new, I started a project to complete the equivalent of an MBA, using free courses. Platforms were making headlines, and when I learned that leading universities were distributing online courses for free, I was inspired to construct an education rather than pay an exorbitant amount for a degree.</description></item><item><title>How Massive Open Online Courses (MOOCs) Work</title><link>https://osaaminen.github.io/blog/how-mooc-works/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Jan 2021 12:52:36 +0600</pubDate><guid>https://osaaminen.github.io/blog/how-mooc-works/</guid><description>When two Stanford professors decided to offer their artificial intelligence (AI) course online, for free, to anyone interested in taking it, they&amp;rsquo;d expected a few thousand students, tops. But by the start of the class, they had 160,000 enrolled.</description></item><item><title>MOOCs and the Future of Learning</title><link>https://osaaminen.github.io/blog/mooc-future-learning/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Jan 2021 12:52:36 +0600</pubDate><guid>https://osaaminen.github.io/blog/mooc-future-learning/</guid><description>The trend toward MOOC legitimacy in higher education raises questions about where that education is headed. We live in an era of affordable, high-quality education for everyone, opening doors to college and career advancement.</description></item><item><title>The MOOC Revolution</title><link>https://osaaminen.github.io/blog/mooc-revolution/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Jan 2021 12:52:36 +0600</pubDate><guid>https://osaaminen.github.io/blog/mooc-revolution/</guid><description>Paul Kim brings together experts from higher education, business, law, learning analytics and other relevant areas to provide an evenhanded, research-based positioning of MOOCs within the existing educational technology landscape and a base for understanding whether they could reshape the future of education.</description></item></channel></rss>