<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>specializations on Koulutus ja Osaaminen</title><link>https://osaaminen.github.io/nanodegree/</link><description>Recent content in specializations on Koulutus ja Osaaminen</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>Copyright &amp;copy; 2021 [osaaminen](https://osaaminen.github.io)</copyright><lastBuildDate>Wed, 06 Jan 2021 15:27:17 +0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://osaaminen.github.io/nanodegree/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Coding for Everyone: C and C++</title><link>https://osaaminen.github.io/nanodegree/coding-everyone-c/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Jan 2021 15:27:17 +0600</pubDate><guid>https://osaaminen.github.io/nanodegree/coding-everyone-c/</guid><description>This Specialization is intended for all programming enthusiasts, as well as beginners, computer and other scientists, and artificial intelligence enthusiasts seeking to develop their programming skills in the foundational languages of C and C++. Through the four courses, you will cover the basics of programming in C and move on to the more advanced C++ semantics and syntax, which will prepare you to apply these skills to a number of higher-level problems using AI algorithms and Monte Carlo evaluation in complex games.</description></item><item><title>Developing Industrial Internet of Things</title><link>https://osaaminen.github.io/nanodegree/developing-industrial-internet-things/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Jan 2021 15:27:17 +0600</pubDate><guid>https://osaaminen.github.io/nanodegree/developing-industrial-internet-things/</guid><description>In this specialization, you will engage the vast array of technologies that can be used to build an industrial internet of things deployment. You&amp;rsquo;ll encounter market sizes and opportunities, operating systems, networking concepts, many security topics, how to plan, staff and execute a project plan, sensors, file systems and how storage devices work, machine learning and big data analytics, an introduction to SystemC, techniques for debugging deeply embedded systems, promoting technical ideas within a company and learning from failures.</description></item><item><title>Introduction to Cyber Security</title><link>https://osaaminen.github.io/nanodegree/introduction-cyber-security-specialization/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Jan 2021 15:27:17 +0600</pubDate><guid>https://osaaminen.github.io/nanodegree/introduction-cyber-security-specialization/</guid><description>This set of courses are designed to help learners develop a deeper understanding of modern information and system protection technology and methods. Learners will develop a lifelong passion and appreciation for cyber security, which will help in future endeavors. Students, developers, managers, engineers, and even private citizens will benefit from this learning experience. Special customized interviews with industry partners were included to help connect the cyber security concepts to live business experiences.</description></item><item><title>System Issues in Cloud Computing</title><link>https://osaaminen.github.io/nanodegree/system-issues-cloud-computing/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Jan 2021 15:27:17 +0600</pubDate><guid>https://osaaminen.github.io/nanodegree/system-issues-cloud-computing/</guid><description>This specialization is aimed at computer professionals to give them an in-depth experience in developing different layers of a Cloud computing infrastructure including software defined networks, distributed runtime systems, application development, and network function virtualization. Each course is organized as discussion of the technical details pertaining to that topic. Each one-hour video is followed by a hands-on workshop assignment.</description></item></channel></rss>