<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Our Courses on Koulutus ja Osaaminen</title><link>https://osaaminen.github.io/course/</link><description>Recent content in Our Courses on Koulutus ja Osaaminen</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>Copyright &amp;copy; 2021 [osaaminen](https://osaaminen.github.io)</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 02 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://osaaminen.github.io/course/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Build a Modern Computer from First Principles</title><link>https://osaaminen.github.io/course/cs-build-modern-computer-principles/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://osaaminen.github.io/course/cs-build-modern-computer-principles/</guid><description>we will build some elementary logic gates, and then use them to build an ALU and a RAM. We then playe with low-level programming, assuming that the overall computer is actually available. Finally we will assemble all these building blocks into a general-purpose 16-bit computer.</description></item><item><title>CS50's Introduction to Computer Science</title><link>https://osaaminen.github.io/course/cs-cs50/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://osaaminen.github.io/course/cs-cs50/</guid><description>This is an introduction to the intellectual enterprises of computer science and the art of programming with or without prior programming experience.</description></item><item><title>CS50's Understanding Technology</title><link>https://osaaminen.github.io/course/cs-cs50s-understanding-technology/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://osaaminen.github.io/course/cs-cs50s-understanding-technology/</guid><description>This is an introduction to technology for students who don’t (yet!) consider themselves computer persons.</description></item><item><title>Programming for Everybody (Getting Started with Python)</title><link>https://osaaminen.github.io/course/cs-getting-started-with-python/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://osaaminen.github.io/course/cs-getting-started-with-python/</guid><description>This course aims to teach everyone the basics of programming computers using Python. We cover the basics of how one constructs a program from a series of simple instructions in Python. The course has no pre-requisites and avoids all but the simplest mathematics. Anyone with moderate computer experience should be able to master the materials in this course.</description></item><item><title>Brand Management: Aligning Business, Brand and Behaviour</title><link>https://osaaminen.github.io/course/bus-brand-management/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2020 15:27:17 +0600</pubDate><guid>https://osaaminen.github.io/course/bus-brand-management/</guid><description>Professor Nader Tavassoli of London Business School contrasts traditional approaches to branding - where brands are a visual identity and a promise to customers - to brands as a customer experience delivered by the entire organisation.</description></item><item><title>Learning How to Learn</title><link>https://osaaminen.github.io/course/learning-how-to-learn/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2019 15:27:17 +0600</pubDate><guid>https://osaaminen.github.io/course/learning-how-to-learn/</guid><description>This course gives you easy access to the invaluable learning techniques used by experts in art, literature, math, science, and many other disciplines. We’ll learn about the how the brain uses two very different learning modes and how it encapsulates information.</description></item></channel></rss>